How you doing? Good to see you again. I'm good, I'm good seeing you too, man. First thing I'm gonna say is, uh, I'm not
dying for Israel, okay, that's the first thing I'm gonna say. And I don't like
when you come up here and you use the type of rhetoric that you do, you talk
like all these like left-wing positions, and then you go to the last part, which
is, I don't support ethnic cleansing in Palestine. I think you're doing a huge
disservice to pro-Palestinians when you start allowing your, allying yourself
with all these progressives. I don't think it looks good because you have all
these conservatives in here who oppose war, they oppose intervention, in the same
tradition of Pat Buchanan and all the greats that came before him. Not Donald Trump, though, sadly.
Yeah, it is sad, it is sad, I do agree. I mean, he ran on an anti-war ticket, he said he was
gonna, I didn't. Because he lies, right? You gonna let me talk, or you just wanna?
Yeah, true, so. I mean, yeah, you keep, you know, you keep going back to Trump. I don't
think this is part of his plan, I think this is a plan of lobbyists, and this is
not just unique to Trump, it's been a thing since the Democrats, it's been a
thing since the Republicans before him, it's been like this since Truman. I don't
know if you read, like, John Mearsheimer's The Israel Lobby, or anything like that.
Would you agree or disagree with anything like that? Oh, I agree with
Stephen Ault and John Meshama, yeah, for sure. Okay, great. So, I'm just warning, when you
ally yourself with all these leftists, and you come up here and you argue for
immigration, you argue up here that, you know, Trump's this bad criminal, and this
and that, and then you. But you think Trump's bad, too. A bad, I think he's good on some
questions and bad on other things, but let me get to my point here, is you ally
yourselves with guys like, you know, Jewish Voices for Peace, and all those
guys. Great people. Yeah, not really, though. Why? Because they're self-interested in it.
They're not, by definition, they're not. It says it on their home page. By definition, they're not
self-interested, right? They're going against their own community. Are you gonna let me talk? On their
home page, it literally says that, we are here to segregate Judaism from Zionism.
It's very clear they're doing this in their own interest. That's why it
literally says, Jewish Voices for Peace. They're gonna be the good Jews who say
that we don't support Palestine. And then what happens is, you take all these
progressives, you go out there and LARP in the street, and then everyone here who's
conservative, they're gonna vote for the pro-war candidate, because they don't
want to be associated with all the liberals. You're forced to vote for pro-war people.
Poor conservatives. It's either that, or get replaced in my country. What do you want me to do?
Oh, you and your replacement bullshit. Yeah, okay, buddy.
Oh, wow. That's three people so far. Let's keep counting.
We should be nicer to you, otherwise you'll deport us. What a great argument.
This is a free speech debate camp.